hey everyone welcome to my channel if
you're new here i am hajah happy new
year 2022.
in this tutorial i want to demonstrate
the application of a colorful graphic
eyeliner for hooded eyes hooded eyes if
you're not familiar with are eyes with
excess skin covering the lid space and
that is why eyeliner application is a
little tricky now unlike a classic black
eyeliner a colorful eyeliner can be
really fun and unique to wear since i
have brown eyes i think the shade blue
will enhance my eye color further that
is why in this tutorial i will be using
the fenty beauty vivid liquid eyeliner
base side in shade skinny dip
ready to try this out and then let's
jump into this tutorial
[Music]
so first of all we make sure our eyelids
are concealed and set it with
translucent powder then we start right
away with the eyeliner application you
can use any color and eyeliner product
that works best for you i'm using the
fenty beauty skinny dip neon blue
eyeliner we start creating our basic
line which is the line that is applied
on our upper lash line we apply small
strokes and connect them with each other
with the eyeliner starting from the
inner corner up until the outer corner
of the eye important note for hidden
eyes is to adjust the thickness of the
basic line to the available lid space
you have the thickness of the line
should only take up to half of the lid
space and not more because that will
give you the illusion of a bigger lid
space besides the thicker your basic
line the more your hood will be
emphasized after applying the basic line
we now go back to the inner corner and
frame the tear duct with the eyeliner to
create an illusion of more elongated
eyes next step is to indicate the length
and height of your wing on hidden and
droopy eyes we want to lift and elongate
the eyes that is why we must place the
wing as high as we can the length of the
wing should not be longer than the tails
of the brow it should be located
diagonally to the tail of the brow hence
we keep our eyes open look straight and
relax into the mirror and draw a small
dot which determines the starting point
of our wing we connect the dot with a
basic line by drawing a straight line up
until the basic line
to complete the wing we now apply a
straight line from the outer corner of
the eye up until the dot during the
application your lashes might get in
between and get painted simply get a
cotton swab and remove the product from
the lashes now after slightly closing
your eyes you will notice a gap close
the gap by applying a line starting from
the wing straight up until the basic
line
now your winged eyeliner is almost
complete fill in the gaps of the winged
liner great job you're halfway there
before creating the graphic line we get
rid of excess product on our eyeliner
brush then we place our eyeliner brush
on top of our wing and without too much
pressure against the skin we draw a
straight line towards our nose bridge
preferably do not take a break while
doing this the straight line should not
be longer than the middle of your lid
you now have the option to make the line
perfect while correcting it like i'm
doing note to do this with a little
product or the rest of the product that
is on your eyeliner brush in case of any
mistakes or unevenness just remove the
line with caution and redo it since
colorful eyeliners will not create a
mess after removing it it is really easy
to correct any mistake
[Music]
now apply some lash primer and mascara
to enhance your lashes it is really
enough to apply only mascara with
colorful eyeliner on since the natural
lashes are more obvious with the
colorful background
[Music]
and if you still go for falsies make
sure they're not too voluminous and have
a thin lash band that will make the
colorful eyeliner pop out even more than
working with dramatic falsies
[Music]
i hope you've enjoyed watching this
tutorial if you did please let me know
by liking and sharing this video comment
down below whether you have tried the
colorful eyeliner on your eyes do not
forget to subscribe and hit the bell
notification to not miss out on the next
tutorial thank you